https://wovoka.space

NAME VLADIMIR POLANSKY

FRONTEND DEVELOPER BATUMI, GEORGIA

CONTACTS VOVOKA.SPACE

SKILLS REACT, GATSBY

TYPESCRIPT, JAVASCRIPT

HTML5/CSS3 (SCSS/MATERIAL UI)

NODE.JS

MONGODB, GRAPHQL, MYSQL REACT TESTING LIBRARY, JEST

GIT, WEBPACK, ESLINT APP DESIGN BEST PRACTICES, MVC

UNDERSTANDING OF UI/UX, AGILE

ABOUT

I love to travel and communicate. I've visited 14 countries. I always happy to meet new people. I like team sports and board games.

I have experience to deliver results within project's resources and time constraints. I know how to design an application that will be extensible in the future and convert it into components that can be easily extended and reused.

I have good communication skills to articulate thoughts clearly. If I don't know something, I'll go and find out. And I'll share this knowledge with a friend.

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

DECEMBER 2021 - NOW

REACT, TYPESCRIPT, JAVASCRIPT, NODE.JS, HTML, CSS

Developing over 15 web apps under the multilevel frontend training program of RSS (30-40 hours of practice per week) and several pet projects. Teamlead experience.

WEDDING/PORTRAIT PHOTOGRAPHER

2011 - 2020

EUROPE

Wordpress, HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, mySQL, SEO, UX/UI, product strategy, customer journey, SMM, marketing, sales, ads, and communication with foreigners.

EDUCATION

THE ROLLING SCOPES SCHOOL

DECEMBER 2021 - NOVEMBER 2022

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Preschool, Stage#1, Stage#2, React

BELARUSIAN STATE AGRARIAN TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

1993 - 1998

ELECTRICAL ENGINEER

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

B1 (KEEP IMPROVING)

BELARUSIAN

NATIVE

RUSSIAN

NATIVE